Preliminary Inventory of the United States Army Air Forces, Air Matériel Command T-2, Air Documents Division Translation Section translations
Hoover Institution Archives
- Box 46
  - Regenscheit: "tests on suction flap wings NACA 23015 with 10% and 15% flap chord,", circa 1944 (Box-folder 46: 19)
  - Lange-Wacke: "Test reports of 3 and 6-component tests on the angularity series of wings of small aspect ratio,", 2 April 1946 (Box-folder 46: 20)
  - "Untitled German document discussing airplane wings,", undated (Box-folder 46: 21)
  - Lockot: "Wing tunnel corrections with steady compressible flow,", circa 1947 (Box-folder 46: 22)
  - Lehmann: "Wind tunnel measurements on a jet angine model with a cold jet, and a wing as a boundry,", circa 1946 (Box-folder 46: 23)
  - Weber: "Wind tunnel tests on Baake-projectile,", 9 April 1946 (Box-folder 46: 24)
  - Liess: "Wind tunnel tests on a bomb model SE 1000 at supersonic speeds,", 3 April 1946 (Box-folder 46: 25)
- Box 47
  - Messerschmitt: "Tabulated data and areodynamic characteristic curces for Me 309 wing airfoil,", January 1943 (Box-folder 47: 1)
  - A. Roth: "Investigation of a twisted swept-back wing at high speeds,", 13 July 1940 (Box-folder 47: 2)
  - Fenner and Gabbert: "Method for making contact prints from flourescent creen images,", December 1943 (Box-folder 47: 3)
  - Weyde: "Projected turbojet fighter with two Hes 011 trubojet engines,", November 1944 (Box-folder 47: 4)
  - Baerner, Zintl, and Zisler: "Blind landing equipment with aircraft fuselage and antennas,", 10 January 1940 (Box-folder 47: 5)
  - Bredt: "Gas kinetics of very high fli9ght speeds,", undated (Box-folder 47: 6)
  - Baur: "Test flight report Me 328 experimental fighter bomber,", November 1942 (Box-folder 47: 7)
  - Kehl: "Wind tunnel tests on a wing of the henschel-device "Zitterrochen" at sub-and supersonic speeds,", 24 October 1944 (Box-folder 47: 8)
  - "Landestoβ und Rollstoβ von Fahrwerken mit Ringfederbeinen,", 8 February 1943 (Box-folder 47: 9)
  - S. Gunter: "Night fighter and destroyer with 2x Hes 011,", 30 November 1945 (Box-folder 47: 10)
  - H. Luetgebrune: "Pressure distribution measurements of swpet-back wings, Second report on swept-back wings,", 1 November 1941 (Box-folder 47: 11)
  - S. Hoerner: "The aerodynamics of three dimensional bodies,", August 1944 (Box-folder 47: 12)
  - Paul Schmidt: "The Schmidt Tube,", 15 June 1944 (Box-folder 47: 13)
  - Hensen: "Wings of constant chord with sweep and twist in yawing,", undated (Box-folder 47: 14)
  - Hauk: "Original photo Kunstoff-Technik,", January 1942 (Box-folder 47: 15)
  - F. Wehrse: "Pressurized cabin symposium,", undated (Box-folder 47: 16)
  - Kraus: "Friction temperatures tests on a longitudinally stressed tubular probe in subsonic and supersonic, 4 March 1945 (Box-folder 47: 17)
  - W. Kuch: "Recent investigation on glasses and sealing materials for altitude chambers,", undated (Box-folder 47: 18)
  - H. Doetsch: "Profile drag of airfoils,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 47: 19)
- Box 48
  - Voight: "Hish speed development of Me 262,", March-Novemeber 1944 (Box-folder 48: 1)
  - Doetsch: "Miscellaneous wing tunnel data on laminar flow,", April 1943 (Box-folder 48: 2)
  - Ludwieg: "Swept wings at high velocities,", 12 August 1940 (Box-folder 48: 3)
  - Krettner: "Symmetrical lift distribution for a wing without and with sweep (per Weissinger),", 20 July 1944 (Box-folder 48: 4)
  - Bearbeiter: "Interference measurements on a rectangular wing with two drive units,", 5 August 1944 (Box-folder 48: 5)
  - Oswatitsch, Klaus: "Computations of critical mach numbers,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 48: 6)
  - "Miscellaneous wind tunnel data on laminar flow,", undated (Box-folder 48: 7)
  - Koster: "Measurements on NACA airfoil 0 00 12-0.55 45 with split flaps and with a nose split flap,", undated (Box-folder 48: 8)
  - Geottingen: "Wind tunnel tests on various wing profils,", 6 September 1941 (Box-folder 48: 9)
  - Baerner: "Directions for replacing the short-wave fixed antenna by self-excitation of the airplane,", April 1939 (Box-folder 48: 10)
  - Hoke: "Stress measurements on landing gear,", undated (Box-folder 48: 11)
  - Focke-Wulf: "Correction factors for high mach nos. as found by flight test of FW 190 airplane,", January 1944 (Box-folder 48: 12)
  - Messerschmitt: "Speed performance of fighter Me 262,", June 1943-February 1945 (Box-folder 48: 13)
  - "Me 262 A-1 airplane handbook part 1 fuselage,", January 1944 (Box-folder 48: 14)
- Box 49
  - Ludwieg: "Subsonic and supersonic wind tunnel measurements on a stablilization of a long distance rocket,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 49: 1)
  - Knacke: "Report on works of the "parachute department,", undated (Box-folder 49: 2)
  - Puckett and Conti: "Aerodynamic characteristics of the WVA Kochel wind tunnel,", 7 July 1945 (Box-folder 49: 3)
  - Pressel: "Flow above curced walls,", undated (Box-folder 49: 4)
  - Dobbrack and Knothe: "Four kinds of pursuit courses,", 28 May 1947 (Box-folder 49: 5)
  - J. Rotta: "Contribution to the calculation of turbulent boundary layers,", 1 July 1950 (Box-folder 49: 6)
  - Messerschmitt: "Aerodynamic comparisons of jet aircraft,", undated (Box-folder 49: 7)
  - Peucker: "Optical ultra-red proximity fuze,", undated (Box-folder 49: 8)
  - Kurzweg: "aerodynamic development of the anti-aircraft rocket "Wasserfall",", 15 March 1945 (Box-folder 49: 9)
  - "Instructions for use and maintenance of the statoscope-recording camera,", 1 October 1941 (Box-folder 49: 10)
  - F. Blasberg: "Directions for using the FBM hard chomium plating baths,", 14 December 1944 (Box-folder 49: 11)
  - "Laval type bucket base of the turbine disc 109-001.150-005.13,", 12 July 1944 (Box-folder 49: 12)
  - Eggink: "On shock waves with separated flow,", August 1943 (Box-folder 49: 13)
  - Jacobs: "6-component on four trapeze wings with sweep position,", 10 March 1944 (Box-folder 49: 14)
  - W. Pinsker: "The aerodynamic coefficients of the lateral motion,", undated (Box-folder 49: 15)
  - W. Kruger: "Six-component measurements on a cranked swept-back wing,", undated (Box-folder 49: 16)
  - Ludwieg: "Swept wings at high velocities,", undated (Box-folder 49: 17)
  - W. Jacobs: "pressure distribution measurements on arrow wings of contant chord in symmetrical airflows,", December 1943 (Box-folder 49: 18)
  - Geissler, Ludwieg, and Cox: "Control apparatus for the project "Wasserfall" 144 g. Kdos,", 29 March 1946 (Box-folder 49: 19)
  - Kosel: "Committee meeting on production of steel spars,", undated (Box-folder 49: 20)
  - F. Schultz and Grunow: "Three contributions to the theory of the nonstationary one-dimensional flow of gases,", June 1946 (Box-folder 49: 21)
  - W. Kuch: "Recent investigations on glasses and sealing materials for altitude chambers,", undated (Box-folder 49: 22)
- Box 50
  - Braun and Scharn: "Influences of the fuselage on the yaw-roll moment,", undated (Box-folder 50: 1)
  - O. Foster: "USSTAF in Eruope, Director of Intelligence, Pans and Training Division, Reel Contents List,", circa 1949 (Box-folder 50: 2)
  - O. Foster: "USSTAF in Eruope, Director of Intelligence, Pans and Training Division, Reel Contents List,", circa 1949 (Box-folder 50: 3)
  - A. Lippisch: "Pressure distribution measurements at high speed and oblique blower stream,", 25 September 1942 (Box-folder 50: 4)
  - Truckenbrodt: "Systematic calculations in the aerodynamics of the airfoil,", undated (Box-folder 50: 5)
  - Walter and Heger: "Experimentelle und theoretische Untersuchungen ϋber das flatterverhalton des pfeilflϋgels,", 22 March 1945 (Box-folder 50: 6)
  - Hobusch: "Spotwelded steel spars,", undated (Box-folder 50: 7)
  - Wehrse: "Discussion on sealing problems,", 22 March 1944 (Box-folder 50: 8)
  - Wehner: "The noise-proofing of aircraft cabins,", undated (Box-folder 50: 9)
  - R. Heimberger: "Aerial reflector sights,", 27 July 1948 (Box-folder 50: 10)
  - Poppendick: "Device Kiel Z "infrared search apparatus",", 29 September 1944 (Box-folder 50: 11)
  - Muttray: "On the application of the momentum measurements method to the direct determination of the profile drag in windtunnel studies,", June 1937 (Box-folder 50: 12)
  - "A highly sensitive relay,", 27 November 1941 (Box-folder 50: 13)
  - Voight, Walter, and Heger: "Transparencies,", undated (Box-folder 50: 14)
  - Voight, Walter, and Heger: "Graphs,", undated (Box-folder 50: 15)
- Box 51
  - "Strength specifications for the Me 261 airplane", 6 December 1938 (Box-folder 51: 1)
  - Lemme: "Force tests and pressure distribution on a wing with bent nose, slat, camber-and extension flap,", undated (Box-folder 51: 2)
  - Kucheman and Weber: "On the flow around ring-shaped coling part III then ring profiles,", 8 Febuary 1946 (Box-folder 51: 3)
  - "Junkers, Dessau, and Dispersals electrical report,", undated (Box-folder 51: 4)
  - "Report on Dornier Werke G.m.b.H. Friedrichshafen, Germany and dispersals,", June 1945 (Box-folder 51: 5)
  - Kruger: "Wind tunnel tests on a complete 4-motored model with and without boundary layer control,", undated (Box-folder 51: 6)
  - Jacobs: "Six component tests conducted on 3 sweep wings,", undated (Box-folder 51: 7)
  - Kuch and Perkuhn: "Investigations on the elastic properties of transparent synthetic materials,", 28 August 1940 (Box-folder 51: 8)
  - Kosel: "Determination of mean sheet thickness S1 for the design of monocoque wings,", undated (Box-folder 51: 9)
  - H. Hoke: "Stress measurements on landing gear in landing and in rolling,", undated (Box-folder 51: 10)
  - "Time study on various aircraft parts,", April 1942 (Box-folder 51: 11)
  - "Kochel wind tunnel documents,", 29 January 1946 (Box-folder 51: 12)
  - Kruger: "Noise problems in aviation,", undated (Box-folder 51: 13)
  - Kruger: "Collection and comparison of various design and means,", undated (Box-folder 51: 14)
  - Perkuhn and Kuch: "The thermal expansion of synthetic glasses,", 8 March 1941 (Box-folder 51: 15)
  - Rotta: "Roll-mechanical foundations for the design of nose-wheel landing gear,", undated (Box-folder 51: 16)
  - Ruster: "Introduction fundamentals, tolerances, and fits,", undated (Box-folder 51: 17)
  - B. Regenscheit: "Tests on drag reduction at high mach-numbers of a wing by suction removal of boundary layer separated in regions of unsteady compression,", undated (Box-folder 51: 18)
  - ludwieg: "Wind tunnel tests in subsonic and supersonic regions on a model of the anti-aircraft rocket "Rheintocher RIII",", 1 March 1945 (Box-folder 51: 19)
  - Krettner: "Symmetrical lift distribution for wings without and with sweep, according to Weissinger,", undated (Box-folder 51: 20)
- Box 52
  - Lienarz: "Comparison of high speed tests on serval airplane models,", Febuary 1947 (Box 52: 1)
  - Bergander: "Character and measurements of self-alignment forces on the landing gear,", Undated (Box 52: 2)
  - Steimel, Daellenbach, Labus, and others: "Very short wave oscillators,", October 1942 (Box 52: 3)
  - Heine: "Untersuchungen uber Entduppelung von Bordfunk meβgeraten auf Grand der Ruckstrehlungsmoduletion,", 17 January 1945 (Box 52: 4)
  - Ruett: "Field strength of magnesium alloy 35079 for aircraft components,", September 1940 (Box 52: 5)
  - F. Schinidt: "Calculations of airflow in the vicinity of fuselages part 2 analysis of a fuselage system,", June 1945 (Box 52: 6)
  - H. Lindemann: "High speed tests on a Me 163 B tailless fighter model,", October 1943 (Box 52: 7)
  - W. Walcher: "Ion Sources,", October 1944 (Box 52: 8)
  - "Testing of the airborne search radar Rossendaal/Halbe in operation,", undated (Box 52: 9)
- Box 53
  - Dimpker: "The effect of bending frquency on the critical velocity when two degrees of freedom,", undated (Box 53: 1)
  - A. Mueller: "Steal instead of light metal in airplane construction,", April 1942 (Box-folder 53: 2)
  - F. Scholkemeier: "Lift and control surface moment measurements on simple wings with flaps with constant ratio and cord ratio at various Reynolds numbers and blockage,", June 1946 (Box-folder 53: 3)
  - Koehler: "Hyrdualic deep-drawing tests with magnesium alloy,", November 1943 (Box-folder 53: 4)
  - Neubauer: "Elimination of radio reception interference inaircraft, III: causes of radio interference in finished airplanes and their elimination,", undated (Box-folder 53: 5)
  - "Propagation of electrical waves of all frequencies,", December 1943 (Box-folder 53: 6)
  - Schaeffer: "The effect of different types of electromagnatic shields,", undated (Box-folder 53: 7)
  - Schlichting: "Exact methods for calculating laminar boundary layer control,", undated (Box-folder 53: 8)
  - Ruschitska: "German radar transmitter Bione IFF apparatus as a radar jammer,", February 1942 (Box-folder 53: 9)
  - "Preliminary description of the antenna with reflector wall 602,", February 1945 (Box-folder 53: 10)
  - Haeusler: "Design of an electric 4 cm antiaircraft gu,", May 1945 (Box-folder 53: 11)
  - "Calculations on wing flutter,", June 1945 (Box-folder 53: 12)
  - H. Kafka: "Deflection of electromagnetic waves,", undated (Box-folder 53: 13)
  - Tollmien and Schaefer: "Rotationally symmetrical supersonic flow part 1 to 12,", October 1941 (Box-folder 53: 14)
  - Mende: "Radar location of long-range rockets,", December 1944 (Box-folder 53: 15)
  - Lehnert: "Report on three-component measurements of the A4-V13/e,", 19 September 1941 (Box-folder 53: 16)
  - "Tactical and technical directions for broader development of airborne radio and radar apparatus,", November 1944 (Box-folder 53: 17)
- Box 54
  - W. Knackstedt: "Evaluation of compiled ballistic data on bodies of revolution,", October 1939 (Box-folder 54: 1)
  - R. Sauer: "Summary of steady compressible flow theory,", August 1940 (Box-folder 54: 2)
  - "Photoelectric detector and warning device,", November 1940 (Box-folder 54: 3)
  - bachem and Dieckmann: "Detectors with high resolving power for underwater sound waves,", August 1940 (Box-folder 54: 4)
  - Morsberg: "Use of reflection amplifying dipoles for indentification signals,", September 1947 (Box-folder 54: 5)
  - "New method for solution of algebraic equations with complex roots,", November 1944 (Box-folder 54: 6)
  - Gresky: "Airborne radar search equipment,", April 1942 (Box-folder 54: 7)
  - Walther: "Most favorbale flight-path of gliding, winged missiles,", June 1942 (Box-folder 54: 8)
  - F. Krum: "Pressure-proof electrical connections for high altitude aircraft,", 23 March 1948 (Box-folder 54: 9)
  - "Torsion tests and shearing stress tests on monocoque panels and box spars,", March 1942 (Box-folder 54: 10)
  - Schulse: "IFF equipment "Erstling",", June 1942 (Box-folder 54: 11)
- Box 55
  - Voight, Walter, and Heger: "Ueber das Prandtl –Busemannsche Veriahren zur zeichnerischen Verfolgung ebener Ueberschall-strӧmungen,", undated (Box-folder 55: 1)
  - Riegels and Brand: "Stream functions and velocity fields of spatial source paths and their handy use for the determination of the contour and pressure distribution of rotational bodies with examples,", undated (Box-folder 55: 2)
  - A. Zickler: "Neue fototechnische Übertragungsverfahren,", undated (Box-folder 55: 3)
  - Brodel: "Theory of two-dimensional symmetrical catch-diffusors,", undated (Box-folder 55: 4)
  - Braun: "Problems found in the stress analysis of the swept wing,", 15 January 1945 (Box-folder 55: 5)
  - Brennecke: "Measurements on a model of a jet-propulsion nacelle,", 7 January 1943 (Box-folder 55: 6)
  - E. Seiferth: "The yawing wing,", undated (Box-folder 55: 7)
  - Lehmann: "Wind tunnel measurements on jet engine models with cold jet,", undated (Box-folder 55: 8)
  - W. Lehmann: "Wind-tunnel investigations of jet propulsion models with cold jet,", 4 November 1943 (Box-folder 55: 9)
  - Gothert: "High speed measurements on airfoils of the series NACA 230 with different thickness ratios,", undated (Box-folder 55: 10)
  - Noeggerath: "Report on code names for rocket fuels,", undated (Box-folder 55: 11)
  - G. Schuls: "Aerodynamic rules for the installation of jet engine nacelles,", undated (Box-folder 55: 12)
  - Kruger: "Wind tunnel measurements and computations on the problem of the shrouded propeller,", 21 January 1944 (Box-folder 55: 13)
  - Wager: "Airfoil boundary suction for Ar 234 fighter bomber,", Febuary 1943 (Box-folder 55: 14)
  - Lappisch: "Preformance theory of airplanes with jet propulsion,", undated (Box-folder 55: 15)
  - Lindemann: "High speed measurements on Me-262,", September 1942 (Box-folder 55: 16)
  - H. Lindemann: "High speed wind tunnel tests of scale model of Me 262,", September 1942 (Box-folder 55: 17)
- Box 56
  - Gothert: "High speed measurements on Mustang airfoil 1.6 50 13.6-0.0825 39,", undated (Box-folder 56: 1)
  - Gothert: "Pressure distribution and impulse lss diagrams of the airfoil 0 00 06-1.1 30 at high subsonic velocities,", undated (Box-folder 56: 2)
  - B. Regenscheit: "Tests on a suction wing NACA 23015 with and without curved nose,", 1 December 1940 (Box-folder 56: 3)
  - W. Kochanowsky: "Stresses on landing gear in landing and with rolling,", July 1934 (Box-folder 56: 4)
  - Regenscheit: "Suction flap wing 43015,", undated (Box-folder 56: 5)
  - "High-speed measurements on a NACA airfoil #000 12-1,1 30 at various angles of attack,", August 1941 (Box-folder 56: 6)
  - Hansen: "Trapeze wing with sweep and twists in yawing,", undated (Box-folder 56: 7)
  - Retert: "Tests for the recovery of guided high speed missiles,", undated (Box-folder 56: 8)
  - Groth: "On the evaluation of density fields obtained by interference methods at high subsonic velocities,", undated (Box-folder 56: 9)
  - Lamla: "On the ray path in Schlieran-pictures of simple two dimensional shock waves,", 31 November 1944 (Box-folder 56: 10)
  - Zobel: "Advances in optical flow measurements,", Febraury 1934 (Box-folder 56: 11)
  - Gothert: "Comparison between drop tests and wind tunnel tests regarding drag of bombs at high subsonic velocities,", 17 April 1942 (Box-folder 56: 12)
  - E. Moller: "Six-component tests on rectangular wings with dihedral and sweep in a large yaw angle range,", undated (Box-folder 56: 13)
  - E. Moller: "6-component tests on wing-fuselage combinations with a swept trapezoidal wing,", undated (Box-folder 56: 14)
  - Gothert: "High speed measurements on airfoils of the series NACA 230 with different thickness ratios,", 23 May 1944 (Box-folder 56: 15)
  - E. Moller: "6-component tests on wing fuselage combination,", undated (Box-folder 56: 16)
  - hempel: "Effect of swept-back wing at high mach numbers,", 2 February 1944 (Box-folder 56: 17)
  - E. Moller: "Six component tests on wing-fuselage combination,", 20 Novemeber 1940 (Box-folder 56: 18)
  - Gothert: "Pressure distraction and impulse loss diagrams of the airfoil 0 00 09-1.1 30 at high subsonic velocities,", undated (Box-folder 56: 19)
  - Gothert: "Pressure distribution impulse loss diagrams of the airfoil 0 00 12-1.1 30 at high subsonic velocities,", undated (Box-folder 56: 20)
  - Gothert: "pressure distribution and impuilse loss diagrams for the airfoils NACA 0 00 15-1.1 30 at high subsonic velocities,", undated (Box-folder 56: 21)
  - Gothert: "Pressure distribution and impulse loss diagrams of airfoil 0 00 18-1.1 30 at high subsonic velocities,", undated (Box-folder 56: 22)
  - Gothert: "Pressure distribution diagrams for the airfoil 2 35 12-o.55 40 at high subsonic velocities,", undated (Box-folder 56: 23)
  - Gothert: "Pressure distribution diagrams for the airfoil 0 00 12-0.55 40 at high subsonic velocities,", undated (Box-folder 56: 24)
  - B. Gothert: "High velocity measurements on profiles of the same thickness ratio with various cambers in the high velocity wing tunnel 2.7m. dia.,", undated (Box-folder 56: 25)
  - Gothert: "High speed measurements on airfoils of the series NACA 230 with different thickness ratios,", 23 May 1944 (Box-folder 56: 27)
  - Groth and Kemnitz: "High velocity measurement on complete model of Ar 234,", 22 March 1944 (Box-folder 56: 28)
  - Doetsch: "Drag tests on various wing forms on the Fieseler Device and investigations on the noise and vibration of the motor on the profile drag,", undated (Box-folder 56: 29)
- Box 57
  - "German aviation documents,", undated (Box-folder 57: 1)
  - H. K. Onnes: "Report on new expirements with superconductors,", April 1947 (Box-folder 57: 2)
  - Schade: "Numerical solution of the Possio integral equation of the oscillating airfoil in steadysubsonic flow,", undated (Box-folder 57: 3)
  - Winkler: "A novel product planimeter,", undated (Box-folder 57: 4)
  - Kraus: "Calculation and discussion of skin-temperatures TBL for the project "Wessefal" in flat-and inclined trajectory,", undated (Box-folder 57: 5)
  - H. Preussler: "The calibration of cold-drawn sections,", November 1949 (Box-folder 57: 6)
  - K. Hilscher: "The wobbler error in a gyro compass,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 57: 7)
  - Focke-Wulf: "The shear strength of plexiglass and reilit,", April 1940 (Box-folder 57: 8)
  - "Interrogation report on junkers personnel concerning aircraft structure specifications,", August 1945 (Box-folder 57: 9)
  - Kaul: "Statistical analysis of service stress on airplane wings,", undated (Box-folder 57: 10)
  - Schade: "Numerical solution of the Possio integral equation of the oscillating airfoil in steady subsonic flow,", undated (Box-folder 57: 11)
  - P. Ruden: "Scoop-diffusors,", undated (Box-folder 57: 12)
  - Rautenburg and Wenk: "Generalized presentation of the lateral stability theory,", 1 January 1939 (Box-folder 57: 13)
  - Romberg: "Parachute jump from high altitudes,", 23 June 1941 (Box-folder 57: 14)
  - Ruden: "Wind tunnel tests on flat, symmetrical collector-diffusors,", undated (Box-folder 57: 15)
  - Scholz: "Calculation of trajectory of A-4 rocket,", undated (Box-folder 57: 16)
  - Bauer: "Investigation of the applicability of a reciever equipped with lead sulfide cells for navigation in fog,", undated (Box-folder 57: 16)
  - Goth and Kemnitz: "High velocity measurements on complete model of Ar 234,", 22 March 1944 (Box-folder 57: 17)
  - Focke-Wulf: "Safe shear flow for skin and spar web of F-W wing,", undated (Box-folder 57: 18)
  - Chr. Junge: "Turbulence tests in the higher atmosphere,", March 1983 (Box-folder 57: 19)
  - G. Schmitz: "Course of motion, impact forces and spring strokes in the landing of a nose-wheel airplane,", circa 1943 (Box-folder 57: 20)
  - "Strength specifications for the Me 261 airplane,", November-December 1938 (Box-folder 57: 21)
  - "Circuit diagrams of the Me-262 electrical system,", 22 July 1949 (Box-folder 57: 22)
  - F. Feldmann: "Compressibility effects in aviation,", circa 1946 (Box-folder 57: 23)
  - Focke-Wulf: "Determination of the static values of wing profiles from tables,", undated (Box-folder 57: 24)
  - Voight, Heger, and Walter: "Wind tunnel tests on wing flatter oscillations with external excitation at 2 and 3 degrees of freedom,", undated (Box-folder 57: 25)
- Box 58
  - Jehle: "Investigation on the wing weight of the Ju 87 and Ju 88 airplanes,", 25 July 1939 (Box-folder 58: 1)
  - Brennecke and Keydell: "Tests on a roll angle-steady flight body,", undated (Box-folder 58: 2)
  - Kochel: "The spark illumination equipment for windtunnel schlieren optics,", 5 August 1945 (Box-folder 58: 3)
  - Karlschagen: "Wind tunnel studies on the rolling controls of missle C2/E2 for project "Wasserfall",", 2 March 1944 (Box-folder 58: 4)
  - Hertl: "Purifying metal melts by ultrasonic oscillation,", 15 April 1935 (Box-folder 58: 5)
  - W. Ernsthausen: "The influence of aerodynamic properties upon the field of sound and radiation output of an air screw,", undated (Box-folder 58: 6)
  - Pinsker: "Influence of air density and flight velocity on the laternal motion of airplanes,", undated (Box-folder 58: 7)
  - Perkuhn and Kuch: "the thermal expansion of synthetic glasses,", 8 March 1941 (Box-folder 58: 8)